Hey guys, let me show you other method to dump ls as.
So this will be Microsoft's internal.
It's brought down the 11.0.
So you can download the product and you can extract the file and you can save in any
of the directory.
Then open the command prompt.
So instead of render 32.exe, so you can use the product to dump an ls as in a successful
manner.
Let me open this.
Let me redirect to the directory which I extract or the product.
So, the command will be the prompt and acceptable to enable some to do some privilege.
So what we need to dump ls as, ACC, ET, T-U-E-U-L-A, okay.
And M-A to the M-A parameter to put the PDF of ls as, so if you find the bit, we know how
to find the P-D-N-R-3-S-E-D-M-I-P-D-D-I-4-D, let me save this in a dump directory.
Name this ls as, the D-M-T, let me execute this.
So now the dump count has reached and the dump complete, 58 in megabits of data has
been returned in three seconds, 0.3 seconds, let me verify that, okay, so here you can
see the ls as, dump has been created or 320 just now.
So this is one of another method to dump ls as, in a quick manner instead of, or R-D-L-32.with the com, S-V-C-D, let you can use a
problem to dump ls as from the machine, okay.
So hope you enjoyed this technique, we'll meet you in the next video.
See you guys, bye bye.